(Penny:)Honey. Shush, shush, shush.
(Leonard:)You shush. I'm happy.
I wanna talk about it.
[LEONARD CHUCKLES]
You know what my mother would say?
She'd say...
(Leonard:)...because you were not loved by your
father and I was not loved by my mother...
(Leonard:)...that having sex is our way of making up
for intimacy we didn't get as children.
(Penny:)Why would you bring that up right now?
(Leonard:)I don't know. Foreplay?
(Penny:)So you're saying
you're not having sex with me...
(Penny:)...you're having sex with your mother?
Um, I'm gonna go with no.
(Penny:)That is the sickest thing
I have ever heard.
Uh, come on, you're trying to have sex
with your father, and I'm okay with that.
PENNY:
Get out!
(Leonard:)She said shush. I should have shushed.
[BOTH SINGING JOURNEY'S
"ANY WAY YOU WANT IT"]
- All night